In the last lesson,
在上节课
you made a number of recommendations using different methods.
你使用不同的方法做出了多次推荐
However, we didn't really look at how we could know
但是 我们并没有查看
if our users would even like our recommendations.
用户甚至是否喜欢我们的推荐
In practice, we could look at a particular metric of interests,
在实践中 我们在实施推荐系统之前
prior to implementing our recommendation.
可以查看一个特定的指标
This might be a metric associated with user engagement, downloads, or revenue.
例如与用户互动、下载量或收入相关的指标
We could then look at the metric again after
在实施推荐引擎之后
implementing the recommendation engine to see the impact.
我们可以再查看该指标 看看效果如何
All of the ideas related to the experimental design portion of this course,
在实践中选择如何以最佳方式实现推荐引擎时
will come in handy when choosing how to best implement your recommendations and practice.
在这门课程的实验设计部分学习的所有概念都会派上用场
But what if you would like to get a sense of how well
但是如果你想在针对真实用户使用推荐引擎之前
your recommendation engine might work before using it on real users?
先了解下推荐引擎的效果 该怎么办？
Similar to machine learning techniques,
我们可以采用与你已经熟悉的
you already are familiar with.
机器学习技巧相似的技巧
It's a good idea to split your data into training and testing partition.
建议你将数据拆分为训练部分和测试部分
You will fit the recommender on the training set,
你需要将推荐系统应用到训练集上
and then evaluate the performance on the test set.
然后使用测试集评估效果
If your collected ratings are made over time,
如果收集的评分是随着时间的推移获得的
you should make the newest data your test set.
你应该将最新数据作为测试集
This way, you avoid using future data to make predictions on past data.
这样就可以避免使用未来数据预测过去的数据
Now, take as an example Allie,
以 Allie 为例
who liked Avengers and Spiderman.
她喜欢《复仇者联盟》和《蜘蛛侠》
We might recommend to her Rocky and the Incredibles.
我们可以向她推荐《洛奇》和《超人总动员》
However, if she still hasn't seen them,
但是 如果她依然没有看过这两部电影
then we don't know if these predictions are actually good.
那么我们不知道这些预测实际上是否效果不错
Instead, if we predict ratings for every movie,
我们可以预测每部电影的评分
then we can compare the ratings of the movies a user actually watch to our predictions.
然后将用户实际观看的电影的评分与我们的预测进行比较
If we predict for every user item combination in the test set,
如果我们能够预测测试集中的每个用户-项目组合
we can understand how well our recommendation engine is working.
那么我们就知道推荐引擎的效果如何
This is just one of the reasons,
这只是接下来将学习的下个技巧
the next technique we'll look at for making recommendations has become extremely popular.
变得异常热门的原因之一
It provides predicted ratings for every user item pair.
它会提供每个用户-项目对的预测评分
This then allows you to use metrics like mean
使我们能够在将推荐引擎
squared error or mean absolute error to measure how well
部署到实际生产环境当中之前
your recommendation system is performing across
使用均方误差或平均绝对误差
all user anime combinations before you have to deploy it into the world.
衡量推荐系统在所有用户-项目组合上的效果